<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Brookgreen Gardens</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Brookgreen Gardens</string>
    <string name="hgl">Heron, Grouse, and Loon;;</string>
    <string name="dq">Don Quixote;Ana Hyatt Huntington (1876 &#8211; 1973)\nAluminum, 1947;Huntington envisioned Cervantes\' famous subject as a pitiful character, rather than a comic one. She depicted him dazed and confused at the moment after he has lost his joust with windmills. His dispirited horse, Rocinante, was first modeled in 1937 from local horses at the studio in Atalaya, the Huntington\'s winter home at Brookgreen. After becoming the first sculptor to use aluminum in 1932, it was often her medium of choice.</string>
    <string name="sjt">The Saint James Triad;Richard McDermott Miller (1922 &#8211; 2004)\nBronze, 1996 &#8211; 1997\nGift of the Sculptor;This over-life-size sculpture was the subject of a book, <i>Voices in Bronze</i>, describing its inspiration, creation, and challenges. Miller placed three figures within box-like frames to contrast soft curves with hard geometric lines, a device he had used in other works. The frames provide support and visual interest without confining the contemplative figures. The title is derived from Saint James, New York, hometown of the individual who commissioned the work.</string>
    <string name="fwg">Flying Wild Geese;Marshall M. Fredericks (1908 &#8211; 1998)\nBronze, 1967;Marshall Fredericks studied at the Cleveland School of Art, with sculptor Carl Milles in Stockholm, and on a traveling scholarship through Europe. This sculpture was designed for the Alvan Macauley Memorial located in Elmwood Cemetery, Detroit, MI. A much admired work, other castings are placed at the Foreign Ministry Building in Copenhagen, Denmark; Kellogg Foundation Headquarters in Kalamazoo, MI; and Frederick Meijer Gardens and Sculpture Park in Grand Rapids, MI; in addition to other locations.</string>
    <string name="col">Circle of Life;Harold "Tuck" Langland (born 1939)\nBronze, 2001\nGift of Tuck and Janice Langland;Using the metaphore of dance, this group of four figures represents the cycles of human life, four seasons, four elements, and four directions. Each figure has an accompanying poem written by the sculptor.\n\n<i>Being</i>\nHe is the south with the sun high in the day\nHe is summer with growth abundant\nHe is air and the breath of life</string>
    <string name="cop">Child of Peace;Edward Fenno Hoffman III (1916 &#8211; 1991)\nBronze, 1962\nGift of the family of Anne Morrison Chapman;A love of children and small creatures inspired the sculptor\'s depiction of a young boy nestling a dove against his chest. The tender portrayal of childhood presents Hoffman\'s sculptural philosophy "I want to animate my sculpture with an inner life that people sense when observing it." This work received the Dr. Maurice H. Hexter Prize for sculpture in the round from the National Sculpture Society in 1979.</string>
    <string name="ttf">Tortoise Fountain;Janet Scudder (1873 &#8211; 1940)\nBronze, c. 1908;Janet Scudder was among the first group of American artists to specialize in figures for garden settings. An admirer of the work of Frederick MacMonnies, she was inspired further by Italian Renaissance sculpture during a visit to Florence in 1908. According to the artist, her aim was to please and amuse the world with her sculpture. She accomplished this through a strong feeling for style and emphasis of line.</string>
    <string name="rgw">Ring of Bright Water;Kent Ullberg (b. 1945)\nBronze\nGift of Mr. &amp; Mrs. Irwin Belk;A native of Sweden, Kent Ullberg studied at the Swedish Konstfack School of Art in Stockholm and at art museums in Germany, the Netherlands, and France. Inspired by the classic story, <i>Ring of Bright Water</i>, by Scottish nature writer Gavin Maxwell, Ullberg presented a pair of otters playing underwater. He stated, "Otters are...the most charming and playful animals...Their supple bodies lend themselves to the swirling composition."</string>
    <string name="twf">Timber Wolf Family;William Henry Turner (born 1935)\nBronze, 1990\nGift of Dorothy R. Blair;A self-taught artist, William Turner experiments with modeling and casting techniques and has built his own foundry in order to have greater control over the creation of his work. At a young age, he became interested in taxidermy and sculpture after Robert H. Rockwell, noted animal sculptor and curator of the American Museum of Natural History, retired near Turner\'s home and eventually because his mentor. In 1989, Turner was commissioned by the museum to create this work as a memorial to Rockwell.</string>
</resources>